<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:dc="http://purl.org/dc/elements/1.1/" xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/">
    <channel>
        <title></title>
        <link>undefined</link>
        <description>undefined</description>
        <lastBuildDate>Sun, 25 Aug 2024 16:49:38 GMT</lastBuildDate>
        <docs>https://validator.w3.org/feed/docs/rss2.html</docs>
        <generator>Joplin Pages Publisher</generator>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[1-100 (2016-2017)]]></title>
            <guid>da74a6387a5748988b4e391e300c3013</guid>
            <pubDate>Thu, 22 Aug 2024 22:26:58 GMT</pubDate>
            <content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>1- “Time and space are the most complex knowledge to comprehend. Time was created after the Big Bang so does the space. Hence, what was before the Big Bang?” …Inamullah Mumtaz… 2016</p>
<br class="jop-noMdConv" />
<p>2- “Atheists do the biggest mistake by denying God, because they have no knowledge what was before the Big Bang. There ideology starts after the Big Bang where as the knowledge of the metaphysical sciences started before.” …Inamullah Mumtaz… 2016…</p>
<br class="jop-noMdConv" />
<p>3- “Two kinds of processes of creation are to be found in the Holy Quran. One before the Big Bang, the creation of spirits or souls which requires no time. Another after the Big Bang, where a baby needs full nine months of gestation period to be developed completely. Although, the soul was created long before the Big Bang.” …Inamullah Mumtaz… 2016</p>
<br class="jop-noMdConv" />
<p>4- “Scientifically, there is nothing before ‘ONE’. Zero has no value if it is taken alone. Hence! Allah is the one from the beginning and everything comes after Him not before. That is why the Holy Quran uses powerful words to describe Allah in such wordings, “that He is alone (not one)”” …Inamullah Mumtaz… 2016</p>
<br class="jop-noMdConv" />
<p>5- “All knowledge has been put into prophet Adam’s mind. We all are sharing the knowledge genetically in fractions from him. Exfoliation of knowledge has become the natural process of humans’ intellectual evolutionary process (not Darwin’s).” …Inamullah Mumtaz… 2016</p>
<br class="jop-noMdConv" />
<p>6- “Anything is possible either extra-terrestrial or paranormal. Science advancement has shown us enormous proofs now. So, if we read any great Saint flew from one city to another we should not mock. It is same as if you tell a cave man that the whole movie could be transferred through a Bluetooth from one device to another without looking at it!”</p>
<br class="jop-noMdConv" />
<p>7- “We can never have a complete knowledge of stars due to the speed of light. Many stars which are born today will reach to us after million of years due to their far distances.”</p>
<br class="jop-noMdConv" />
<p>8- “All the elements in the Universe are running in Cosmic Balance. If anything changes slightly, it will destroy the purpose. This is what Allah says in the Holy Quran, “Heaven is bound in cosmic scale/balance”. If sun loses its slight gravity, it will let earth swift away. If opposite, it will burn it. Imagine this! which Science has come to know now.”</p>
<br class="jop-noMdConv" />
<p>9- “Materialistic earth bounds our flesh too in materialism. Spirit has much power to do things but earth makes us heavy and weak. Earth’s gravity decides our ages and life spans.”</p>
<br class="jop-noMdConv" />
<p>10- “Contemplation is the only tool which makes you near to Allah.”</p>
<br class="jop-noMdConv" />
<p>11- “This era’s education makes us brainwashed intellectuals whose real ingenuity is only on the information rather knowledge.”</p>
<br class="jop-noMdConv" />
<p>12- “Islam is the only just socio-politico-economic system. Capitalism, Communism/Socialism and secular democracy are failed to provide justice.”</p>
<br class="jop-noMdConv" />
<p>13- “Mankind has become intellectual hypocrite, as knowing all the propensities, absurdities and atrocities but still do it. Having a disease of hyper-normalization.”</p>
<br class="jop-noMdConv" />
<p>14- “Immodesty should not be defined with modernism. If modernism is ‘immodesty’, that is something else.”</p>
<br class="jop-noMdConv" />
<p>15- “Women’s veil is the most important social security issue. Unveiled women creates the biggest commotion in the society. Even western great think-tanks know it.”</p>
<br class="jop-noMdConv" />
<p>16- “Women have become eye candy toys to the world now. They have lost their integrity under the flag of modernism.”</p>
<br class="jop-noMdConv" />
<p>17- “Men are the present of the Era and women are the future. Men are responsible for the bread and women to raise children for the future.”</p>
<br class="jop-noMdConv" />
<p>18- “The biggest reality of this world is “Death”. Our intellectual hypocrisy has reached to its climax. We don’t fear death. But we fear not having our own premises.”</p>
<br class="jop-noMdConv" />
<p>19- “Without certain knowledge, you will always suffer from the host of inferiority complex.”</p>
<br class="jop-noMdConv" />
<p>20- “We do feel that this world will perish, but strange invisible dangling carrot stops us.”</p>
<br class="jop-noMdConv" />
<p>21- “Time and space are the need of three-dimensional universe. Beyond that we have no knowledge whatsoever.”</p>
<br class="jop-noMdConv" />
<p>22- “Only human beings are the species which have different countenance if you compare to other beings. This is enough proof that mankind is the greatest creation of Allah.”</p>
<br class="jop-noMdConv" />
<p>23- “Our own existence is self-evident that there is life after death.”</p>
<br class="jop-noMdConv" />
<p>24- “If any fear or anxiety of losing something comes to you, don’t fear it. Every tiny fraction is under the control of Allah. When the steering turns, you have no idea. All fears are created by Satan in our minds, when you think big it will not harm you anymore. Fear Allah only and always see people under you not above. Fear of poverty and sustenance come from Satan, don’t lose hope and always fight like a strong person like the soldier of Allah.”</p>
<br class="jop-noMdConv" />
<p>25- “Anxiety and fear are self-created things, pray to Allah to show you other doors when you suffer from these things. Sometimes we are failed to see hidden doors and dwell in this disease.”</p>
<br class="jop-noMdConv" />
<p>26- “Many western people are in deep anxiety and dilemma; highest paid treatments are being used in psychology and psychiatry department. This is what happens when you don’t have logical concept of God.”</p>
<br class="jop-noMdConv" />
<p>27- “Music, Songs, Media, Movies and Sports are the biggest weapons of illuminati/Dajjal/Capitalist to evade people from understanding the evil motive of theirs.”</p>
<br class="jop-noMdConv" />
<p>28- “On what grounds Christians have Bikinis Shows when Christ said, “Anyone who sees a woman to lust after her hath committed adultery already in his heart”.”</p>
<br class="jop-noMdConv" />
<p>29- “We all are getting brainwashed into one objective of west, " New World Order/Jew World Order subconsciously".</p>
<br class="jop-noMdConv" />
<p>30- “The biggest weapon of devil is to destroy the family system. Procreation of illegitimate children is the goal. Morally understanding has been removed from the family system. Americans are no more obliged to get married as the bastard will get more benefits from the government than a legitimate one.”</p>
<br class="jop-noMdConv" />
<p>31- “Strange sense has been developed in the Western culture, in severe cold women’s legs are naked and men are in full clothes. 99 percent of women in the west are not saved at nights in the tunnel according to British Statistics.”</p>
<br class="jop-noMdConv" />
<p>32- “Islam has given us self-boasting confidence to put our hands on our children’s heads and proclaim! they are legitimate. Can west do that! According to the statistics, France has more than 70 percent bastard children. And Bible says, “A bastard shall not enter into the congregation (Church/Synagogue) till his/her 10th generation.”</p>
<br class="jop-noMdConv" />
<p>33- “Create a free time in your life, otherwise you will never be able to contemplate the secret of the heavens and the earth.”</p>
<br class="jop-noMdConv" />
<p>34- “You cannot run away from death, better stop flimflamming and hoodwinking, come to the point and accept the right path.”</p>
<br class="jop-noMdConv" />
<p>35- “Too much reading of philosophies will make you insane. Too much reading of the books is the weariness of flesh.”</p>
<br class="jop-noMdConv" />
<p>36- “Western civilization is busy in three philosophies, experimentalism, existentialism and reconstructionalism. These are the obvious reasons why they have become secular.”</p>
<br class="jop-noMdConv" />
<p>37- “Study the ontology, epistemology and axiology of Islam to know the truth. Barking media makes more sound than contemplating Islam. When a chickpea is hollow from inside it produces more sound than the filled one.”</p>
<br class="jop-noMdConv" />
<p>38- “Interest/Usury banking system makes poor becomes poorest and rich becomes richest.”</p>
<br class="jop-noMdConv" />
<p>39- “No civilization has ever brought better just social system than Islam in the history of mankind.”</p>
<br class="jop-noMdConv" />
<p>40- “If woman has a privilege of being boss, she understands the feelings of womenfolk only same for men too. Only creator knows the best for both.”</p>
<br class="jop-noMdConv" />
<p>41- “There are two types of women in the world, one who becomes Cleopatra and destroys the nation and one who is stampeded like animals. Islam gives the optimal place for woman. Socially woman is not equal to man but in the creation, they both are equal.”</p>
<br class="jop-noMdConv" />
<p>42- “Woman has many weaknesses which makes her failed to become a leader, had it been for women to become leaders, Allah would have chosen prophetess among them too. Physiologically women are soft and fragile and not be exposed in the society. If they are bosses, they will never be able to do just decisions according to psychologist. Their temperament fluctuates according to their menses/periods.”</p>
<br class="jop-noMdConv" />
<p>43- “Wearing helmet is a security for a biker, but wearing veil is an oppression for a woman!!!”</p>
<br class="jop-noMdConv" />
<p>44- “Too much diplomacy and bureaucracy in a social life make untrustworthy environment and greedy, ostentatious materialistic image.”</p>
<br class="jop-noMdConv" />
<p>45- “Man should be alpha male in all social matters and woman should be alpha female in nurturing kids.”</p>
<br class="jop-noMdConv" />
<p>46- “A human is ready to make 1000 hasty retreats and lies rather than to get rid of his prejudices.”</p>
<br class="jop-noMdConv" />
<p>47- “British left their educational curriculum after the colonial rule and left the note of contention for the Islamic Educational system.”</p>
<br class="jop-noMdConv" />
<p>48- “Adultery and fornication in west is like eating peanuts now. Alhumdulillah! we Muslims have not reached to such sickness where our wives, daughters, sisters and mothers are exposing themselves in the simulated immodest scenes. And our guardians would self-boast that they are “Stars”.”</p>
<br class="jop-noMdConv" />
<p>49- “If an employer uses the same toilet which the employee uses, then the real face of him/her will be judged.”</p>
<br class="jop-noMdConv" />
<p>50- “People who sneak other people’s activities are the host of inferiority complex.”</p>
<br class="jop-noMdConv" />
<p>51- “Experiment and knowledge will lead you to the right experience. And right experience will lead you to the perfect life.”</p>
<br class="jop-noMdConv" />
<p>52- “Sometimes this world feels weird to me, it seems to be an illusion and boredom. Monotony makes you sick from this world.”</p>
<br class="jop-noMdConv" />
<p>53- “Learning of educational Psychology and Philosophy of Islam must be incumbent on every student.”</p>
<br class="jop-noMdConv" />
<p>54- “Democracy is the real autocracy which is disguised as a wolf in sheep’s clothing.”</p>
<br class="jop-noMdConv" />
<p>55- “Pakistan is severely suffering from Laissez Faire Administration in the governmental departments. Due to this, poor society has been suffering a lot.”</p>
<br class="jop-noMdConv" />
<p>56- “The biggest reality of this life is death and the real reality of this universe is the Day of Judgment. Are we ready for it?”</p>
<br class="jop-noMdConv" />
<p>57- “Nationalism injection creates ugliest infection in our society. We can move mountains and rocks through it.”</p>
<br class="jop-noMdConv" />
<p>58- “What is the magic wand which runs the economy? It is the lust of materialism which booms and recess. New World Order is the one global system where your mind will be indulged in deep materialism.”</p>
<br class="jop-noMdConv" />
<p>59- “Novus Ordo Seclorum, see the U.S Dollar bill and research yourself. New World Order is equal to the Jew World Order.”</p>
<br class="jop-noMdConv" />
<p>60- “Marrying more than one woman at the same time is a mockery in West, but having sex without marriage 24/7 with agreement is reformation and modernism.”</p>
<br class="jop-noMdConv" />
<p>61- “Since the creation of Pakistan, we are suffering from the Fiscal, Monetary and Regional policies.”</p>
<br class="jop-noMdConv" />
<p>62- “Rothschild Family is the one who purchased Palestine and gave to the Zionist Jews under the Balfour’s Agreement.”</p>
<br class="jop-noMdConv" />
<p>63- “Total freedom is total annihilation.”</p>
<br class="jop-noMdConv" />
<p>64- “Islam is not against the freedom; it is against the total freedom.”</p>
<br class="jop-noMdConv" />
<p>65- “There is no liberal Islam. It is a package deal either take it or leave it.”</p>
<br class="jop-noMdConv" />
<p>66- “Without the Khilafah, Islam is only the religion of rites and rituals.”</p>
<br class="jop-noMdConv" />
<p>67- “Allah shows everyone the rite of ‘passage but most of the people ignore it.”</p>
<br class="jop-noMdConv" />
<p>68- “Popular democracy doesn’t reform anything. It is just the musical chair game for the politicians.”</p>
<br class="jop-noMdConv" />
<p>69- “We don’t need cancer to kill ourselves today, our self-made laws are enough intro-punitive.”</p>
<br class="jop-noMdConv" />
<p>70- “Today’s politics is only extra-punitive dogging.”</p>
<br class="jop-noMdConv" />
<p>71- “Oil nationalization is the biggest cause which instigated wars in the world.”</p>
<br class="jop-noMdConv" />
<p>72- “Shell, Chevron, Exxon, Mobil, Gulf, BP and Texaco are the seven ugly sisters who have eaten the world’s peace.”</p>
<br class="jop-noMdConv" />
<p>73- “The most dangerous thing is the illusion of wealth the oil brings.”</p>
<br class="jop-noMdConv" />
<p>74- “Governments don’t rule the world, Goldman Sachs rules. Jewish Orthodox Bank Loan Investors.”</p>
<br class="jop-noMdConv" />
<p>75 “Prophet Muhammad PBUH said, Modesty and Faith are parallel things. If you lose modesty, faith goes with it.”</p>
<br class="jop-noMdConv" />
<p>76- “Black Gold and Gold are the only two assets of this era which create ugliest destruction in the world. In spirituality, I think these two are the evil food of Dajjal’s/Antichrist’s preparation.”</p>
<br class="jop-noMdConv" />
<p>77- “Rothschild Family, Rockefeller Family, Goldman Sachs Group and Bilderberg Group are the powers who destroy the peace of the world through their insatiable lust of materialism. I rather call them the hosts of Dajjal/Antichrist. Gold, Black Gold, Bank, Media/News, Usury, Monetary, Insurance, Loan, Inflation, Deflation, Hollywood, Yellow Journalism, Food Control, Brainwashing and Socio-Politico-Economic system all these are under their control. Islam is the biggest threat for them today. These groups instigated wars in the past and has tendency to create in future. In reality, they control all the governments. They have no religion; they are total secular or atheist. This flood was instigated by the Jews to take complete revenge from the Christians. We can see that what is happening in west due to their agenda. Morally and Socially western civilization has been doomed. Now, this flood is coming to India subcontinent in the shape of Bollywood. New World Order is the main agenda of the Jews to make all people to follow one system which is totally free based secular. Popular based democracy. This flood is coming to Muslim countries now and unfortunately the elite class of ours has already been indulged into it.”</p>
<br class="jop-noMdConv" />
<p>78- “Most of the people don’t know that Israel, India and U.S.A are neo-cons. Which means they are the member of Neo-conservatives. This is the democratic party of U.S.A.”</p>
<br class="jop-noMdConv" />
<p>79- “Cultural Marxism and Multiculturalism are the same formulas which were postulated by Akbar the Great as ‘Deen-e-Elahi’. Through this stick, western world has been drowned into severe confusion. We need another reformer like Shah Waliullah of Delhi in our times too.”</p>
<br class="jop-noMdConv" />
<p>80- “Yellow Journalism is the only tool left to fulminate Islam now. This job has a great demand in every country. To lie day and night.”</p>
<br class="jop-noMdConv" />
<p>81- “Since 1947, Pakistan is still searching for its identity due to confused secular lifestyle.”</p>
<br class="jop-noMdConv" />
<p>82- “In 1882, British conquered Egypt only to control Suez Canal which was built by the blood of the Egyptians through French engineers. Excessive loans and tricks by European Jewish Bankers caused this conflict which forced Ismael Pasha to sell the shares of Suez Canal Company to the Queen of England to remove the debts. England gave 20 million dollars to Ismael Pasha. After this, Egyptians were not having any economical growth due to 50% of shares in the bank of England. The revolt occurred from the natives of Egypt which caused British invasion for 75 years under the pretext of national peace in Egypt. Why Suez Canal was so important? European ships had to go around the Cape of Good Hope to reach Arab Peninsula and India. This route was discovered by Portuguese sailor Vasco Dagama. Pirates on Red Sea route caused so much trouble for the travelers and it was long too. The point is obvious here, how these Christians and Jews stole our efforts and labeled us “terrorists” in this era! They acted themselves like a holy robot and peace makers.”</p>
<br class="jop-noMdConv" />
<p>83- “Shah of Iran Muhammad Raza Pahalvi’s extravagancy reminds me the temple of Nimrod, Pharaoh and Nebuchadnezzar. His ministers said that Shah believed Islam to be the biggest cause of uncivilization in Iran. He banned veil and ordered to shave off the beards too. He forced people to wear western clothes. He seems to be the sesame twin brother of Ata Turk Kamaal Pasha of Turkey. It is sad to see how our dynasties have been ruined down under the western interest.”</p>
<br class="jop-noMdConv" />
<p>84- “Two things destroy a weak man, ‘money and status’. After that he goes blind.”</p>
<br class="jop-noMdConv" />
<p>85- “Everyone has forgotten that he or she is a Muslim. But everyone remembers his/her national identity.”</p>
<br class="jop-noMdConv" />
<p>86- “French revolution came only to change the political laws. Bolshevik (Communism) and Mensheviks (Fraction version of Communism) revolution came only to change the economical laws in Russia. Khomeini in Iran came only to change the social laws. Xinhai revolution of China came only to change the political laws. But when Prophet Muhammad PBUH came, it was the total change of socio-politico-economic system. In other words, Islam is the only religion which brought the total revolution.”</p>
<br class="jop-noMdConv" />
<p>87- “Karl Marx the writer of ‘Das Kapital’ and ‘Communist Manifesto’ was a Jew and sponsored by Rothschild Family which instigated Communism/Socialism in Russia. His maternal grandfather was the Dutch Rabbi. His partner who helped him was the German atheist Friedrich Engels. Imagine, ideology was concocted in Germany and implemented in Russia by Vladimir Lenin.”</p>
<br class="jop-noMdConv" />
<p>88- “Jews took great revenge from the Christians due to their past atrocities at the time of Diaspora. Karl Marx (Jew) gave ‘Das Capital’ to apply communism and on other hand Adam Smith the founder of Capitalism wrote ‘The Theory of Moral Sentiments’ and ‘An inquiry into the Nature and Causes of the wealth of Nations’ his Magnum Opus. They both fought each other badly and totally funded by Rothschild Family with great interest rates. The reason why America fought against Russia in Soviet War, as Communism gives power to every Tom, Dick and Harry in economical structure. America played evil trick by brainwashing Muslim countries to fight against Russia under the pretext of religion.”</p>
<br class="jop-noMdConv" />
<p>89- “Why capital is need to the Jewish Bankers? There are three main reasons; a) Market Competition, b) Entrepreneurial Abilities and c) Unequal Distribution of Income. In this system, the owner/entrepreneur will be the venture capitalist and whenever he makes good money all profit will go to him alone. There is no optimal division/salary and accountability of wealth regarding to the production. And this is the cause which created Feudalism in many countries. This society will only increase poverty and richness to selective people. If entrepreneur fails in business new doors will be opened. Bank Drafts/Over Drafts, high interest rates and end will be grave only.”</p>
<br class="jop-noMdConv" />
<p>90- “Why capitalism hates communism? Two main reasons; a) All the people own 'the means of production (factories) and b) Redistribution of wealth. This system means if you need coffee shop, government will make it and all the workers of shop will have equal money to enjoy. This system was not palatable for Jewish Bankers.”</p>
<br class="jop-noMdConv" />
<p>91- “West is trying its best to eliminate social system of Islam by paying millions to NGOs (non-governmental organizations). Trust me, West has succeeded in destroying our political and economical system already. Hollywood, Bollywood and Lollywood are the typical examples. They are busy day and night just to destroy family values and morality in the culture. On which grounds Pakistan has been entertaining fashion shows? Commotion of Dajjal/illuminati has been reached to its culminating point. Economical and Political secular system have already been applied globally. Only the thing which still Muslims have is the social/family moral values which western world is trying day and night to destroy. So, the best Jinn is T.V which is working for Dajjal. West wants to wash off all these moralities from Islamic world. Many conferences were being done to emancipate women from the houses. Cairo conference, Beijing Conference etc.”</p>
<br class="jop-noMdConv" />
<p>92- “Islam was started by the Arabs of desert then it was fallen into the hands of Kurds &amp; Turks. Kurds created Ayyubis dynasty and these Turks created four major dynasties. a) Turkaane Taimoori (Mughals of India), b) Turkaane Safavii (Iran), c) Turkaane Saljuuki (Middle East), d) Turkaane Usmaani (Anatolia, Asia Minor, East Europe till Siege of Vienna)</p>
<br class="jop-noMdConv" />
<p>Note: Islam will again return back to the Arabs according to the Hadith of Prophet Muhammad PBUH.”</p>
<br class="jop-noMdConv" />
<p>93- “Time is the fourth dimension of space according to Albert Einstein. And that is technology of this age. America has no moral values in their civilization. The only sale-point they have is technology which they can self-boast about.”</p>
<br class="jop-noMdConv" />
<p>94- “Europe brainwashed Arabs beautifully against Turks of Usmani Khilafah (Turkish) by injecting the superiority of the language and cast. Arabs must be superior to others. So, this is way nationalism was created among the Arabs to destroy the Ottoman Empire of Turkey.”</p>
<br class="jop-noMdConv" />
<p>95- Western civilization is dead already, only the thing which makes it alive is technology.</p>
<br class="jop-noMdConv" />
<p>96- “According to the report of Rand Corporation (American Non-Profit Think Tank), There are four types of Muslims in the world. a) Fundamentalist (who thinks Islam is not only rites but a complete Socio-Politico-Economic system, DEEN) b) Traditionalist (typical clergy who love rites and rituals and have no concept of changing the current false system) c) Modernist (people who doesn’t accept orthodox Islamic values, who are reformed in thinking, who manipulates Quran and Sunnah easily) d) Secularist (who accepted western ideologies fully by ignoring Islam, Nominal Muslims) What are the actions applied to all these four by RAND CORPORATION think tanks? a) Kill the Fundamentalist, biggest threat to our civilization. b) Put some secret agencies (spies) who can monitor traditionalist clergies not to join hands with fundamentalists. c) Sponsor them, give them money and bring them on the print and T.V media. d) No action required. Note: This organization has been taken very seriously in U.S.A among the policy making units.”</p>
<br class="jop-noMdConv" />
<p>97- “I.M.F (International Monetary Fund) is the worst trap for those countries which West doesn’t want to prosper.”</p>
<br class="jop-noMdConv" />
<p>98- “After the era of Guided Caliphates, Islam was declining but Muslims were inclining. The social laws were only for the people not for the rulers and the kings.”</p>
<br class="jop-noMdConv" />
<p>99- “There is no such a thing ‘Islamic Banking’. You cannot separate yourself from the state banks. And all of them relate to the Federal Reserve Bank in somehow.”</p>
<br class="jop-noMdConv" />
<p>100- “Passive Hedonism is the disease which makes us forget our human morality in the social life.”</p>
]]></content:encoded>
        </item>
    </channel>
</rss>